A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Sigma Xi FA239
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University collection of Sigma Xi records
undated
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
Rockefeller University
Society of the Sigma Xi
FA239
0.88 Cubic Feet 2 boxes
File Plan note
Former Classification: I 650-3
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Scope and Contents
Types of records include: charters, meeting minutes, correspondence, forms, grant material, reports, and memorabilia.
Arrangement
As received.
Medical education
- Sigma Xi (Box 1)
- Forms (Box 1)
- [Memos], 1983 (Box 1)
- Sigma Xi - Honorary Members (Box 1)
- Current (Box 1)
- [University Charter] (Box 1)
- Business (Box 1)
- 1981 (Box 1)
- [Membership correspondence], 1981 (Box 1)
- [Nominations], 1980 (Box 1)
- Business Meeting, 1989 May (Box 1)
- Initiation, 1979 March (Box 1)
- 1977-1978 (Box 1)
- [Scientific Research Society - National Lectureships Program] (Box 1)
- [Correspondence], 1972 1979 (Box 1)
- Message Form (Box 1)
- [Grants-in-Aid of Research Forms] (Box 1)
- [Letterhead] (Box 1)
- [Forms] (Box 1)
- [Membership List] (Box 1)
- Nominations Forms (Box 1)
- Initiation Forms (Box 1)
- [Lists] (Box 1)
- Admissions in Process (Box 1)
- National Meeting, 10/1979 (Box 1)
- Membership Certificate (Box 1)
- Membership Old (Box 1)
- [General Information] (Box 1)
- Information Sheet (Box 1)
- Sigma Xi National Dues, Constitution, Policies (Box 1)
- Membership, 1975-1976 (Box 1)
- Membership, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
- Membership, 1977-1978 (Box 1)
- Membership, 1979-1980 (Box 1)
- Membership, 1980-1981 (Box 1)
- Membership, 1981-1982 (Box 1)
- Membership, 1982-1983 (Box 1)
- Membership, 1983-1984 (Box 1)
- Membership, 1984-1985 (Box 1)
- Membership, 1985-1986 (Box 1)
- Membership, 1986-1987 (Box 1)
- Membership, 1987-1988 (Box 1)
- Membership, 1988-1989 (Box 1)
- Membership, 1989-1990 (Box 1)
- Membership, 1990-1991 (Box 1)
- Membership, 1991-1992 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 2)
- Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 2)
- Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 2)
- Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
- Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 2)
- Treasurer's Report, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
- Treasurer's Report, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
- Treasurer's Report, 1977-1978 (Box 2)
- Treasurer's Report, 1978-1979 (Box 2)
- Treasurer's Report, 1979-1980 (Box 2)
- Treasurer's Report, 1980-1981 (Box 2)
- Treasurer's Report, 1981-1982 (Box 2)
- Treasurer's Report, 1982-1983 (Box 2)
- Treasurer's Report, 1983-1984 (Box 2)
- Treasurer's Report, 1984-1985 (Box 2)
- Treasurer's Report, 1985-1986 (Box 2)
- Treasurer's Report, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
- Treasurer's Report, 1987-1988 (Box 2)
- Treasurer's Report, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
- Treasurer's Report, 1989-1990 (Box 2)
- Treasurer's Report, 1990-1991 (Box 2)
- Treasurer's Report, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
- Treasurer's Report, 1992-1993 (Box 2)
- Chapter Lists (Box 2)
- Miscellaneous Sigma Xi Objects (Box 2)